Thank you guys for having us over.
谢谢你们请我们过来吃饭
Yeah, this is fun, couples night.
多有意思  夫妻派对
I don't know why we don't hang out...
我不知道为什么我们不多来几次
...with married couples more often.
这样的夫妻聚会
Because every time we do...
因为每次我们吃饭
...you make jokes about swinging
你总是开玩笑要夫妻交换
and scare them away.
把他们吓跑了
You mean that Portuguese couple?
你是指那对葡萄牙人
Yeah, like you wouldn't have done it.
就像你没做过蠢事一样
Hey, you guys, I have great news.
嗨  大伙  我有个好消息.
We're kind of in the middle of dinner.
罗斯  我们似乎还在吃饭
Oh, well, I already ate, but sure.
呃...我已经吃过了  不过...好吧
Guess what happened at work today.
猜猜今天工作时发生了什么
A dinosaur died a million years ago?
一只恐龙在一百万年前死了
Try 65 million years ago. And then try...
应该是六千五百万年前  请闭嘴
My tenure review board met today,
我的终身任职考察会议今天开了
and I hear it's looking really good.
我听说进展得不错.
Yeah, do you have any idea
你知道这在理论界里
what this means in academic circles?
意味着什么吗
I am gonna get laid.
我可以留下来了.
- Hi, you guys. - Hey.
-嘿  大伙  -嘿
Oh, ltalian.
意大利风味
No one-- No one wanted seconds, right?
还有人好说话吗
No, I'm good.
不  不  我很好
Guys, you're never gonna believe it.
嘿  你们一定不相信
This headhunter called me.
猎头给我打了电话
Gucci:著名意大利奢侈品品牌
说古驰要面试我
Gucci wants me.
古驰要聘用我
- I'm up for tenure. - Congratulations.
-我快终身任职了  -祝贺你
You too. What are the odds?
你也是  真巧
Guess what?
猜猜发生了什么
I finally got that seed out of my teeth.
我终于把那个种子从我的牙齿里弄出来了.
I don't know who I'm happiest for.
我都不知道最应该为谁高兴了
I do. He's been working on that all day.
我知道  他一整天都在弄它
《老友记》第十季第十四集 "康斯薇拉公主"驾到
《老友记》  第十季  第14集  "康斯薇拉公主"驾到
Hey, Mon, was it weird
嘿  莫妮卡
changing your name to Geller Bing?
把你的姓改成盖勒·宾奇怪吗
No. No, it felt nice to acknowledge this.
不  不  让人们知道也挺好的
- Where'd you go to do it? - The--
-你是在哪办的   -呃...
The Ministry of Names...
姓名部门
...Bureau.
...局
You never did it.
你没有改过
I'm sorry. It's just the idea of--
我很抱歉  变成正式的宾家人
Of being an official Bing.
让人想想就...
Hey, I will have you know that--
嘿   我得让你知道...
Who am I kidding? Let's call the kid Geller
我真是在开玩笑  就让孩子姓盖勒算了
and let Bing die with me.
让宾随着我到死
- Here you go. - Thanks.
-给你  -谢谢
Honey, would you want me to take your name?
亲爱的  你想要我随你的姓吗
Oh, it's up to you.
随便你吧
It's your name.
这是你的名字
You've gotta live with it.
是要跟随你一辈子的
Let's see. Call me Mrs. Hannigan.
试试吧  叫我汉尼根夫人
Mrs. Hannigan?
汉尼根夫人
What? Can't you see I'm in the middle of something?
什么 没见我忙着呢吗
I like it.
我喜欢
- Hey, guys. - Hey, Joe.
-嘿  大伙  -嘿  乔伊
We've got a couple of things
还有一些东西
we've got to check out at the new house.
我们要去新房子那检查
You want to come?
你想和我们一起去吗
No, thank you.
不  谢了
You're not happy about us moving...
我们搬家你不高兴了
...but you're the only one who hasn't seen the house.
但你是唯一没有看过我们新房子的人.
Yeah, come with us.
是啊  和我们一起去吧
You'll see how close it is.
你会知道那离这里很近
No, it's not close.
不  才不近
in escrow:根据协议由第三方保管  乔伊以为是地名
你说它在"艾斯克柔"
I couldn't even find that on the map.
我在地图上都找不到这地方
Joey, please come.
乔伊  求你来吧
It would mean so much to us.
你对我们真的很重要
You know what?
知道吗
You are my friends.
你们是我的朋友
I want to be supportive.
我要支持你们
I will come with you. Shotgun.
我会和你们一起去的  我要副驾驶座
Damn it.
讨厌
See you guys later.
一会见
We'll pick you up at 11.
我们在十一点接你
So glad you're coming.
真高兴你能来
All right.
好
Good for you.
真不错
That was really mature.
你成熟了
What? No, the only reason I'm going...
什么 不  我去那所白痴房子
...to their stupid house is
唯一原因是
to point out everything wrong with it...
要去说出里面所有的缺点
...so they don't move.
好让他们不搬家
I'm gonna make them stay here.
我要他们留在这里
You're a strange kind of grownup.
你这是种奇怪的成长
Joey, you can't make someone do something
乔伊  你不能让别人
they don't want to do.
做他们不愿做的事
Believe me.
相信我
There's something I've been trying to
有些事我想让
get Mike to do in bed, and--
迈克在床上做  但他...
Can we not talk about that now?
我们现在能不谈那个吗
All right. Prude.
好吧  假正经
Look, Monica and Chandler
听着  莫妮卡和钱德勒
really love this house.
真的很喜欢那所房子
You are not gonna talk them into staying here.
你不应该说服他们住在这里
Hey, I can convince people to do anything, you know?
嘿  我能说服人们做任何事情
I bet I could even get Mike to do that thing.
我打赌我能让迈克做那事
What is it?
到底什么事儿
I am not gonna help you do that!
我才不要帮你做那个
Oh, my God.
哦  我的天
Hi. I'm here to see Mr. Campbell, with Gucci.
嗨  我来见古驰的坎贝尔先生
The reservation's probably under Gucci.
位子也许就是古驰公司预定的
It's spelled like "Gukki"
听着像"嘉琪"
which can be confusing.
也许会弄错
Mr.Campbell's not here yet.
坎贝尔现在还没到
Let me show you to his table.
让我把你带到他的位子
Oh, my God. That's my boss.
哦   我的天  那是我的老板.
You have to seat us somewhere else.
你必须把位子安排在别处
I'm sorry,
我很抱歉
that's always Mr.Campbell's table.
这一直是坎贝尔先生的桌子
But my boss cannot see me.
但我的老板不能在这看到我
I'm interviewing for another job.
我在面试另一个工作
I know. With "Gukki."
我知道  面试"嘉琪"吗
- Rachel? - I'm on a date.
-瑞秋  -我在约会
That's great.
太棒了
Yeah, it is.
是啊
Yeah, you know, it's tough.
你知道  太难了
Single mom. Career.
单身母亲  还要事业
You gotta get out there.
但还是要寻找幸福
Well, you've got a good energy.
你很有精力
- Rachel? - Yes, hi.
-瑞秋  -是的  嗨
- James Campbell. - Hi.
-詹姆斯·坎贝尔  -嗨
- Excuse us. - Please.
-抱歉  -请坐
He's cute.
他很可爱.
So...
那么...
...your resume is quite impressive.
你的简历让人印象深刻
My resume?
我的简历...
I wouldn't-- I wouldn't call
我不会把我的
my online dating profile a resume.
线上约会资料叫做简历
Dating profile?
约会材料
No, I'm-- I'm talking about the work resume.
不  我是说...我是说工作简历
Whatever happened to
现在怎么没人
just singing for no reason?
想唱就唱了呢
Maybe people found it weird.
或许是因为别人会觉得奇怪
So....
那么...
Why do you want to leave Ralph Lauren?
你为什么想离开拉夫·劳伦
What?
什么
- I...I don't. - You don't?
-我  我没有  -你没有
No, I love-- I love it there.
不  我喜欢那里
Well, if you don't want to leave,
如果你不想离开
why are we having this lunch?
为什么我们在这里吃午饭呢
What?
什么
Hugo Boss:德国奢侈品品牌
那是雨果·博斯
This place is so depressing.
这个地方太令人压抑了
If I had to work here,
如果我在这里工作
I'd kill myself.
我会自杀的
But you obviously haven't.
显然你还没
How can I help you?
有什么需要帮忙的
I need to change my name, please.
我想要改我的名字
See, I need to change it because I'm hiding from the law.
我想改掉它因为我在逃避法律
You're fun.
你很有趣
You need to fill out this form.
请填一下这个表格
Okay. Well, just so I know--
好  我想了解下
I don't know how it works. My name is Buffay...
我只是不知道应该怎么做  我姓布菲
...and my husband's name is Hannigan.
我丈夫叫汉尼根
So is it supposed to be "Buffay-Hannigan"
那么应该是"布菲·汉尼根"
or "Hannigan-Buffay"?
还是"汉尼根·布菲"
It can be anything you want.
你想怎样就怎样
Well, not anything.
也不是我想叫什么就叫什么吧
Yeah. Anything.
是的  你想叫啥叫啥
Oh, this could take a while.
哦  那需要花些时间
- Get out of my line. - Okay.
-站到一边去  -好
- Hey. - Hey, Pheebs.
-嘿  -嘿  菲比
Oh, not anymore. I changed it today.
不再是了  我今天改了名字
Oh, I'm sorry, Mrs. Hannigan.
抱歉  汉尼根夫人
Wrong again.
又错了
Apparently, you can change it to anything.
显然你能改成任何你想要的名字
So I thought, "All right,
所以我想"好吧
here's an opportunity to be creative."
这是发挥想象力的好机会"
So meet Princess Consuela Banana Hammock.
所以来见过康斯薇拉·巴娜娜·哈莫克公主
That's what we were gonna name the baby.
那是我想给我们宝宝的名字
- Phoebe. - Princess Consuela.
-菲比  -康斯薇拉公主
You seriously changed your name to that?
你真的把你的名字改成那个了
Okay, so from now on,
好吧  从今往后
we have to call you Princess Consuela?
我们得叫你康斯薇拉公主了
No, I'm gonna have my friends call me Valerie.
不  我会让我的朋友叫我瓦莱丽
- Hey, how did the interview go? - Not good.
-嘿  面试如何  -不妙
You know. I always feel that way after an interview.
你知道吗  面试后我经常也这么觉得
I'll bet it went better than you think.
我打赌结果会比你想得好
Well, I didn't get the job at Gucci
我没有得到古驰的工作
and I got fired from Ralph Lauren.
还丢了拉夫·劳伦的工作
That is a bad interview.
这面试的确不好
What are you talking about?
你在说什么呀
How did this happen?
怎么会这样
My boss was at the same restaurant
我老板在同一家餐厅
where I was having my interview...
我在那里面试
...and he heard everything.
他听见了一切
Later, he calls me into his office
后来他把我叫到他的办公室
and tells me he'll have to let me go...
告诉我他要解雇我
...because I'm not a team player.
因为我没有团队精神
And I said, "Wait a minute. Yes, I am."
然后我说"等等  我有"
And then I had to sit there for 45 minutes...
然后我得在那里坐45分钟
...while he proved that that, in fact, was true.
而他证明了  事实他说的那样
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
哦  真抱歉
Hey.
嘿
What--? What's this?
这...这是什么
Why, it's a bottle of champagne.
是一瓶香槟
Why is this here?
它为什么在这
- Ross. - I guess it's here...
-罗斯  -我想是
...because I got tenure!
因为我得到了终身职位
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
-恭喜你  -恭喜你
This is the single greatest day of my professional career.
这是我职业生涯中最伟大的一天
- Gunther. Six glasses. - Six?
-甘瑟  六个杯子  -六个
You want me to join you?
你要我也喝
I thought Joey was here.
我以为乔伊也在这儿
Five is good.
五个好了
Wow, I'm gonna have a loogey in my coffee tomorrow.
明天我的咖啡里要有大鼻涕了
Israeli champagne.
以色列香槟
And it's vanilla.
还是香草味的呢
I got tenure. I didn't win the lottery.
我得了终身职位  又不是中了彩票
Hey, Rach, so how did your thing go?
嘿  瑞秋  你的事怎么了
Good.
挺好
But I'm not going to hear about that for a couple days.
但是要几天以后再出结果.
Oh, you know what, you're gonna get it.
你知道吗  你会得到工作的
I can feel it.
我能感觉到
Can you?
你能吗
All right, everybody, here's to Ross.
好的  敬罗斯
And to years of hard work finally paying off.
为了多年的艰苦工作终于有了回报
And to knowing that your career
也为了懂得你的工作
doesn't mean everything.
并不意味着所有事情
But also knowing it means a lot.
但也意味着很多
But more importantly, to full, well-rounded lives.
更为了多彩丰富的生活
That center around work.
以工作为中心
- To Ross. - To Ross.
-敬罗斯  -敬罗斯
You know what the best part about this is?
你知道最棒的是什么吗
I can never be fired.
我永远都不会失业
- Oh, God. - No, seriously.
-哦  天啊  -不  说真的
I have job security for life.
我有了终生工作保障
You know? I mean, I never have to worry.
我是说我永远都不会为它而担心
Oh, look at you. Look how happy you are for me.
看看你  看你多为我高兴
No, it's not that. I got fired today.
不  不是那样  我今天被辞退了
And I didn't get the other job.
而且又没有得到新的工作
Rach, I'm so sorry.
瑞秋  很抱歉
Great, I feel like an idiot.
太好了  我觉得自己像个白痴
No, it's okay. You didn't know.
不  没什么  你不知道
Little heads-up would've been nice.
你们就不知道提醒下
Thank you for letting us see the house again.
谢谢你能让我们再看房子
And thank you for explaining to us what escrow means.
也谢谢你给我们解释"契约"的意思
I've already forgotten what you said,
我已经忘了你说了什么
but thank you.
但是  谢谢你
Take as long as you want.
想待多久就待多久
Just let me know when you're through.
你们看完之后告诉我就好
So glad you decided to come.
很高兴你能来
Me too. Yeah, this place is great.
我也是  这地方真好
So happy for you guys.
真为你们高兴
Although, you know, I hope you like fungus.
但是  我希望你们喜欢菌类
- What? - Fungus.
-什么  -菌类
Yeah. Place is full of it.
它们在任何地方都有
No, it's not.
不  才不是
We had an inspection
我们叫人来检测过房子
and they didn't find anything.
他们什么都没找到
Okay. Then I guess I have dry eyes
好吧  我想我毫无原因的
and a scratchy throat for no reason.
眼睛干燥喉咙痛
Maybe it's because you hung your head
或许是因为
out the window like a dog...
来的一路上
...the whole ride here.
你都像狗一样把头伸到窗外
Maybe.
也许是
So this is the living room, huh?
那这就是客厅
It's pretty dark.
真暗啊
No, it's not.
才不是
Are you kidding?
你开什么玩笑
I think I just saw a bat in the corner.
我刚才好像在角落看到只蝙蝠
When your head was hanging out the window,
当你的头伸在车窗外的时候
it didn't hit a mailbox, did it?
没有撞到信箱吧
Maybe.
也许
Look, I just think you guys can do
我只是觉得你们
better than this house, you know?
可以有更好的选择
Or any other house for that matter.
或者可以买到更好的房子
Oh, Joey.
哦  乔伊
We know you're having a hard time with this, but we--
我们知道你觉得不好受  但我们...
We love it here.
真的喜欢这里
Fine! Ok. If you love this house so much...
好吧  好吧  如果你喜欢这所房子
...you should live here. Okay?
你们就住这里吧
I hope you get used to that weird humming sound.
我只是希望你们能习惯那种奇怪的声音
- Joey, we know that's you. - No...
-乔伊  我们知道那是你  -不...
...it's not.
不是的
- Welcome back. - I missed you.
-欢迎回来  -我想你了
- Oh, me too. - So, what's new?
-哦  我也是  -有什么新鲜事
Well, I am no longer Phoebe Buffay.
我不再叫菲比·布菲了
That's great. You changed your name?
太棒了  你改名字了
Yes, I did.
是的
Meet Princess Consuela Banana Hammock.
见过康斯薇拉·巴娜娜·哈莫克公主
- You're kidding, right? - Nope.
-你在开玩笑  -不
- You really did that? - Yep.
-你真的那么做了  -对
You can't do that.
你不能那么做
Why?
为什么
Why? It's fun.
为什么  那很好玩
It's different. No one else has a name like it.
很不同  没有人有那样的名字
Then I'm gonna change my name.
好吧  我也去改我的名字
Great. Okay, what are you gonna change it to?
好  你要改成什么
Crap Bag.
大便·袋
Mike Crap Bag?
迈克·大便·袋
No. No "Mike." No, just "Crap Bag."
不  没有迈克  只是大便·袋
First name: Crap. Last name: Bag.
名大便  姓袋
You're not serious, right?
你不是认真  对吧
Yeah, I'm serious.
我是认真的
It's fun, it's different,
很好玩  很不同
and no one else has a name like that.
没有人用这样的名字
Well, then great.
那好极了
If you love it, I love it.
如果你喜欢  我就喜欢
I do love it. And I love your name.
我的确喜欢  我也喜欢你的名字
I love Princess Consuela.
我喜欢康斯薇拉公主
And I love Crap.
我喜欢大便
- Who are you? - Oh, hi. I'm Joey.
-你是谁   -哦  嗨  我是乔伊
My stupid friends are buying this house.
我的白痴朋友要买这所房子
Who are you?
你是谁
I'm Mackenzie.
我是麦肯齐
My stupid parents are selling this house.
我的白痴父母要卖这所房子
I hate my parents.
我恨我的父母
I hate my friends.
我恨我的朋友
Look, there's gotta be a way
瞧  我们肯定能做一些事
that we can stop this from happening.
不让他们交易成功
Like what?
比如
Okay, you come with me and you tell them that the house is haunted.
你跟我来告诉他们这房子闹鬼
What are you, 8?
这么幼稚  八岁啊你
Okay. Let's hear your great idea.
好吧  你有什么好主意
I don't have any great ideas.
我没有好主意
I am 8.
我八岁
There's gotta be a way. I mean, you know...
一定要想一个办法  我是说...
...if Monica and Chandler move here,
莫妮卡和钱德勒搬走了
and Phoebe's married to Mike...
菲比和迈克结婚了
...that just leaves me and Ross and Rach.
只剩我和罗斯还有瑞秋
You know what I mean?
你知道意味着什么吗
I really don't.
不太知道
What am I gonna do?
我到底怎么办
I feel like I'm losing my friends.
我觉得我要失去我的朋友了
My parents say I'll make new friends.
我父母说我能交到新的朋友
Yeah, sure, easy for you.
当然  对你而言很容易
You're young. Me? I'm set in my ways.
你这么小  我生活都定型了
This is what my mom was talking about.
这就是我妈妈一直说的
Whiners are wieners.
抱怨不休的人都是些失败者
Look, you want your friends to be happy, right?
你希望你的朋友开心  对吧
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. Yeah.
是的  我想是的
Well, if moving here is gonna make them happy,
那么  如果搬到这里来会让他们开心
don't you want them to do it?
你难道不希望他们这样做吗
Yeah. Maybe.
希望啊  或许吧
Then you've gotta let them go.
那你就应该放手
Oh, I hate to admit it, but you're--
我恨承认这个  但你...
You're probably right.
也许是对的
How'd you get to be so smart?
你怎么这么聪明
I read a lot.
我读了很多书.
Just when I thought we could be friends.
还以为我们能成为朋友
Oh, hey, Rach. I just heard. I'm so sorry.
嗨  瑞秋  我刚听说  很抱歉
Oh, thank you....
哦  谢谢你...
You still don't know my name, do you?
还是不知道我的名字  对吗
Well, now I don't have to.
现在我不用知道了
Ross, what is taking you so long?
罗斯  你怎么那么慢
I'm sorry. It's almost as if
抱歉  他们建造这门的时候
this wasn't built for a quick getaway.
怎么不考虑让你搬家能快些呢
Rachel?
瑞秋
Mark? Oh, my God.
马克   我的天啊
How have you been?
你怎么样
Fantastic. You remember Ross.
太好了  你记得罗斯
Sure.
当然
What's with the chair?
搬椅子干嘛
You know, you can't always
你知道  在地铁上
get a seat on the subway, so....
没有座位...
Clever.
真聪明
So how are you?
你最近怎么样
You're not catching me on my best day.
真不巧  今天出点事儿
Yeah, a box full of your desk stuff doesn't say "big promotion."
整箱的办公用品  不像是要升职啊
No, but it's good.
不  但也还好
You know, I'm gonna take some time off...
你知道...我要休息一段时间...
- ...and do charity work. - Are you sure?
-做一些慈善工作  -你肯定吗
We may have something at Louis Vuitton.
LV现在可能需要人
Screw charity work. What do you got?
去它的慈善工作  你有什么消息
Why don't we have dinner and talk?
我们边吃饭边讨论吧
- Great. I'll call you. - Okay.
-我给你打电话  -好吧
Nice to see you again.
很高兴又见到你
Yeah. Yeah. I got tenure.
啊...我有终身职位了
Oh, my God.
哦  我的天.
See? I told you something good would come along.
看到没有  我告诉你好事会来的
And he seemed really nice.
他看起来真不错
I've met him before?
我以前见过他吗
Ross, that's Mark.
罗斯  那是马克
From Bloomingdale's?
布明岱尔百货的啊
You were insanely jealous of him.
当时你嫉妒得发狂
- That is Mark? - Yes.
-那是马克  -是啊
I hate that guy.
我恨他
No, no, no.
不  不  不
You cannot go to dinner with him.
你不能和他吃饭
What? You don't want me to get a job?
什么  你不希望我有这份工作
Yeah, I'm sure he'll give you a job.
当然  我肯定他会给你一份工作
Maybe make you his "sex-cretary."
也许让你当他的"性秘书"
I'm serious. I just don't trust that guy, okay?
我是认真的  我只是不相信他
Ross. You know what--?
罗斯  你知道吗
Okay, let's talk about it later. There comes security.
好  我们以后再谈  保安来了
Oh, I love this street.
我喜欢这个街道
The trees and the big front yards and the actual picket fences.
那么多树  大大的前院  真正的尖桩篱栅
Man, those two dogs are going at it.
那是两只狗干上了
Hey. Where you been?
嘿  你到哪里去了
Oh, just, you know, looking around.
哦  只是随处走走
But you know what?
你知道吗
This house is great.
这房子太棒了
Really? What changed your mind?
真的  什么使你改变了
The little girl who lives here made me feel better about the whole thing.
那个住在这里的小姑娘让我感觉好很多
Joey? There was a little girl who lived here,
乔伊  以前有小姑娘住在这儿
but she died, like, 30 years ago.
但三十年前就死了
What?
什么
I'm just messing with you.
我只是在吓你
That's not funny.
这不好笑
You know I'm afraid of little-girl ghosts.
你知道我害怕小女鬼
Now that you're okay with the house,
现在你喜欢这房子了
do you want to go see your room?
你想看看你的房间吗
What?
什么
I get my own room?
我会有我自己的房间
You don't think we'd buy a house
你不会认为我们
and not have a Joey room, do you?
买了房子却没有给你房间吧
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Hey, can I have an aquarium?
我能有个鱼缸吗
And a sex swing?
加个做爱秋千
No.
不
Why not? I'll keep the tank clean.
为什么不行  我会保持干净的
After you, Ms. Bananahammock.
你先请  巴娜娜·哈莫克女士
Thank you, Mr. Bag.
谢谢  袋先生
- Oh, hi, Rita. - How are you?
-哦  你好 瑞塔  -你最近好嘛
Good. Oh, Rita's a massage client.
瑞塔是一个按摩的客户
Yeah.
哦
Why don't you introduce me?
你为什么不介绍我
Rita, this is my husband.
瑞塔  这是我的丈夫
Why don't you tell her my name?
为什么不告诉她我的名字
Okay, I will. This is-- This is my husband, Crap Bag.
好的  我会的  这是我的丈夫大便·袋
Crap Bag?
大便·袋
If you need an easy way to remember it,
如果你需要记得容易点
just think of a bag of crap.
就把它想象成一袋子大便
- Okay. Excuse me. - Yeah.
-好的  少陪了  -好
Okay, fine, you made your point.
好吧  我知道你的意思了
Can you please just be Mike Hannigan again?
你能再做我的迈克·汉尼根
Only if you'll be Phoebe Buffay.
只要你还是菲比·布菲
How about--? How about Buffay-Hannigan?
布菲·汉尼根怎么样
Really?
真的
Yeah.
是
I'm Phoebe Buffay-Hannigan-Banana Hammock.
我是菲比·布菲·汉尼根·巴娜娜·哈莫克
Do you even know what a banana hammock is?
你知道巴娜娜·哈莫克是什么吗
It's a funny word.
就是个有趣的字
It's a Speedo.
那是一种三角裤
Oh, crap.
噢  糟了
- Hey, is Rachel here? - Nope.
-嘿  瑞秋在吗  -不
She's still at dinner?
她还在吃晚饭
I guess. Why, who's she with?
我想是的  她和谁在一起
That guy, Mark...
是马克
...from Bloomingdale's.
布明岱尔百货那个
She thinks he's just being nice to her.
她认为他只是对她好
But I know he really wants to sleep with her.
但我知道他想和她睡
It's seven years ago.
已经七年了
My time machine works.
我的时间机器起作用了
We ran into him on the street today,
我们今天在路上碰到他
and he said he might have a job for her.
他说也许他有工作给她
But I know he just wants to get into her pants.
但我知道他只是想拉她上床
So, what if he wants to sleep with her?
他想跟她上床又怎样
I mean, she's single, and he's cute.
我是说她单身而且可爱
Excuse me?
什么
Oh, please.
哦  拜托
Yesterday, on the subway, you couldn't stop staring...
昨天在地铁上
...at that woman with the big breasts the whole time.
你不停地盯着一个大胸脯的女人看
For your information, I was staring at her baby.
告诉你  我那是看她的小孩呢
We're about to be parents.
我们就要做父母了
Oh, sorry.
哦  对不起
- Hi, you guys. - Hi. So...
-嗨  大伙  -嗨
...how was dinner?
晚饭怎么样
Oh, it was great. Mark is so sweet.
噢  很棒  马克人很好
Oh, yeah? Yeah, I wonder why?
哦  是吗  我想知道为什么
What could that smarmy letch possibly want?
那个虚情假意的好色者想要什么呢
Oh, Ross. Come on. He is happily married.
哦  罗斯  别这样 他已经结婚了
His wife just had twins.
他的妻子生了双胞胎
Should we send something?
我们应该送点什么礼物吗
How did the job stuff go?
工作怎么样
He offered me one.
他给了我一个工作机会
- That's great. - Congratulations.
-太棒了  -恭喜你
I know, it's amazing.
我知道  那很棒
It's amazing. It's so much better
那很棒  那比我在
than what I had at Ralph Lauren.
拉夫·劳伦要好得多
- The money is great. - Can we--?
-薪水很不错  -我们...
Can we just stop for a second?
我们能停一停吗
Who said something better would come along?
是谁说一切都会好起来的
You didn't believe me.
你不相信我
I told you everything was gonna work out.
我告诉你一切都会有起色
You know what?
你知道吗
This calls for a bottle of lsrael's finest.
这时候该来一瓶以色列佳酿
The job is in Paris.
工作地点在巴黎
I mean, this soap opera is a great gig...
我是说  这肥皂剧是很好的机会
...but am I missing opportunities?
但这样做我是不是就错过机会了
You know, I've always thought of myself as a serious actor.
你知道  我总是觉得我自己是个正经的演员
Should I be trying to do more independent movies?
我是不是应该尝试更多的电影
I don't know.
我不知道
But you know what?
你知道吗
I'm gonna put you on with my bear.
我让我的熊听电话
Hold on.
等等
Hey, Bailey, I need some career advice.
嘿 小熊  我需要一些事业上的意见